Adjie Wiratama SALMAN



PROFILE

Curious, driven and dedicated self-proclaimed machine learning engineer with a focus in deep-learning. Experienced in all things machine-learning related: data engineering, data analysis, model training/selection and pipeline creation. Proficient in python as well as well-known libraries such as pandas, numpy, sk-learn and pytorch. Although experienced, still thirsts for more and even more.

CONTACT DETAILS

github.com/ratboitripleseven

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Citizenship: Indonesian Family: Single without children Languages: English (C1), German (B2), Indonesian (native)

SKILLS

- Python, Pandas, Numpy, Sk-learn, Pytorch, Biopython, Snakemake
- R, Matlab, SQL, Git, C/C++, C, SQL (MySQL)
- MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Pycharm, VS Code, Latex
- Team player, driven, motivated

EXPERIENCE

DEEP LEARNING RESEARCH ASSISTANT at University of Duisburg-Essen 06/2022 - 10/2023

- ♦ Training and evaluating various deep learning architecture (CNN, LSTM, GRU, Transformer) on image and sequential dataset.
- Assisting in selection of evaluation methods for generated images.

INTERNSHIP: LAB ASSISTANT at Huawei Technologies GmbH **08/2021 – 03/2022**

- ⋄ Day-to-day maintenance of Openlab Düsseldorf.
- ⋄ Server maintenance of remote testing suite.
- Analysis of the Matter home protocol.

WORKING STUDENT: LAB ASSISTANT at Huawei Technologies GmbH 02/2021 - 08/2021

- ♦ Assisting in the setup of Openlab Düsseldorf under the department of Programming and Engineering of München Research Center.
- Testing applications of undisclosed OS.

WORKING STUDENT: DATA ENGINEER at SICK GmbH 01/2020 - 04/2020

Continuation of internship responsibilities.

INTERNSHIP: DATA ENGINEER at SICK GmbH 08/2019 - 10/2019

Analysing database of service information: assisting in the identification of critical data to generate added value for customers, assisting in the development of interfaces for a product using SQL and also providing documentation for the interfaces and the development.

EDUCATION

MASTER OF SCIENCE (1.8): Computer Eng.: Intelligent Networked System University of Duisburg-Essen.

2020 - 2024

♦ Thesis title: Identification of Horizontal Gene Transfer by using machine learning.

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (2.3): Computer Eng.: Communications Engineering University of Duisburg-Essen.

2014 - 2020

⋄ Thesis title: Spiking Neural Network.

PROJECTS

HORIZONTAL GENE TRANSFER IDENTIFIER: https://github.com/ratboitripleseven/NewGenes

⋄ Master thesis.

SARS-COV-2 VARIANTS IDENTIFIER:

https://github.com/DSiB-G2/G2-CovPipeline

- ♦ Data science master project at the institute for artificial intelligence in medicine of university hospital Essen.
- ⋄ Creation of a python-based pipeline using the Snakemake workflow for Genome analysis and identification of Covid virus variant.

DEGREE RECOMMENDER:

https://thedatadreams3-gmail-com.github.io/

- Project for the course learning analytics.
- \diamond Creation of degree recommender using natural language processing techniques.